iw.ca 2017-05-29

# Privacy Policy - iWeb

This Privacy Policy governs the privacy practices related to the personal information collected through or by Internap from visitors and users of this website and the website of iWeb Technologies, Inc. This Privacy Policy is intended to comply with U.S. – EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland; Canada’s federal Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and any provincial privacy legislation, including Quebec’s An Act Respecting the Protection of Personal Information in the Private Sector.

Internap respects the privacy of every individual who visits this website, provides personal information to us via interactive features of our website(s) or sends e-mails to Internap via our website(s). This Privacy Policy addresses the information that may be collected through our website(s) and how Internap may use that information. In the event that you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit our website(s) or send us e-mails, please refer to the procedures described below. This Privacy Policy does not cover our use of information collected through any other means other than information collected through the use of our website(s).

## **Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

### Personally Identifiable Information

The information Internap obtains from you is necessary or useful for Internap to provide the products and services or information you have requested and to design new services for your future use, and is provided directly by you in response to our request for the information. In connection with the products and services Internap provides, we may ask you to provide your name, physical address, ZIP code, phone number, e-mail address and the type of services received or requested. Your submission of such information online is deemed your consent to our use of the information as contemplated in this Privacy Policy.

### How We Use the Information

Internap limits the information we collect. We may also collect information that is relevant to you but does not personally identify you. If we collect personal information for a reason other than as specified in this Privacy Policy, we will obtain your consent before or at the time the information is collected or as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

Generally, Internap uses the information to provide the products and services or information you have requested, to personalize your experience on our website(s), to provide customer support, to improve our website(s), to enforce our agreements and policies, to resolve disputes, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts and to design new services for your future use.

Internap may also use the information to notify you about new products and services or offers that we may have available, to provide news about Internap; to send you notifications about planned maintenance related to Internap’s infrastructure or about incidents which might impact your services.

We may contact you on behalf of business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your personally identifiable information to the third party.

### When We Share the Information

Internap shares information within our company to enable us to better understand our customers’ service needs, and to learn how to best design, develop and deliver services to meet those needs. We use your personal information only for the outlined purposes and we do not sell, rent or lease our customer lists to unaffiliated third parties without your consent.

To provide our products and services, we, like many organizations, may use third party service providers for routine services such as hiring other companies to provide services on our behalf, including processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support and service offerings, processing transactions or performing statistical analysis of our services. In such cases, Internap provides only the personal information necessary to ensure the service is delivered and requires that the service provider sign a non-disclosure agreement consenting to keep your personal information confidential and secure and limiting its use to the purpose for which it was disclosed. After the service provider has completed the service, the service provider must either destroy the information or return it to Internap. Internap may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary: (a) to conform to the mandates of the law or comply with legal process served on Internap; (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of Internap; (c) to act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of our services or members of the public, (d) to respond to legal requests, or (e) in connection with the sale of all or substantially all of our assets to which our website(s) relates.

While we use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information is consistent with this Privacy Policy, we cannot ensure that your communications with us will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

All personal information is maintained in a secure location. We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you with the products and services or as long as needed to fulfill the purpose for which the personal information was originally collected.

### Other Information We Collect

Some information may automatically be collected as you browse our website(s). Our web server automatically collects some information such as the user-agent (your web browser type, operating system and platform version, etc.), your Internet service provider’s domain name, the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, the average time spent on our site, pages viewed, information searched for, access times and other relevant statistics.

We also use cookies on our website(s). A cookie is a small data file that websites commonly write to the site visitor’s hard drive when a website is visited. A cookie file contains information that can identify a return visitor each time he or she visits our website. Our website(s) may use cookies as a way to measure activity and traffic patterns on the site to continually improve your experience. A browser can be set to warn the user before accepting cookies. You can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in the browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit our website(s).

### Your Choices

**By providing your information to us, you consent to our use of your personal information for the purposes outlined herein.** We do not collect personally identifiable information about you on our website(s) without your knowledge and all such information we collect you are providing to us. You are not required to provide us with this information; however, if you choose not to provide such information or withdraw your consent to collect, use and disclose your information, we may not be able to provide you with some services and you may not be able to participate in some of the activities on our website(s).

We use the information we collect from you to allow you to participate in the site activities for which the information is collected. For example, when you give us your e-mail address to receive newsletters, information regarding our services and special promotions, your e-mail address will be added to our marketing database. We will not send solicitations via e-mail to you if you request that they not be sent. On each e-mail you receive, you are given the opportunity to unsubscribe. In addition, you can “opt-out” by sending an e-mail to [unsubscribe@internap.com](mailto:unsubscribe@internap.com). Once you unsubscribe, you will no longer receive such e-mails. If you decide to withdraw or refuse your consent, our ability to communicate with you may be diminished and you may limit your access to services that may be of value to you.

### Transfers of Information

Internap will follow this Privacy Policy in our use, disclosure and storage of your personal information and may transfer personal information in furtherance of the purposes for which we collect it. We will transfer your personal information only to Internap companies and third parties as permitted by applicable law in countries where we operate and as described herein. In some cases, we may transmit personal information through third parties or subsidiary companies located in other countries. Given that our web servers, which host our websites, are located within and outside of the U.S., it is possible that personal information about visitors may be transferred from one country to another. Some of these countries may not have the same or similar privacy laws as those applicable to your jurisdiction. Local legislation, courts and tribunals will have jurisdiction over personal information in each country. However, Internap has implemented certain safeguards to help protect your information, including requiring third parties to sign a non-disclosure agreement and requiring destruction by them or return of your personal information to us upon completion of the service. By providing us with your information, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. You may direct any questions that you may have regarding the use, disclosure or storage of your personal information to our VP of Internal Audit.

### Access and Review

If you have questions regarding your personal information collected via our website(s), or wish to change or delete such data from our active databases, please contact us at [privacyinfo@internap.com](mailto:privacyinfo@internap.com). We will provide you with copies of records we have regarding your customer relationship with us, unless applicable law provides otherwise. If you feel that the information in your files is inaccurate at any time, you should bring it to the attention of our VP of Internal Audit.

### Children and Privacy

Our website(s) is not directed at children and most services offered on this site are designed for businesses and adults. We do not knowingly collect information from or about children under 13 years of age.

### Security

We maintain our databases and systems in accordance with general industry standards to reasonably secure all of our commercial information, including information about you. All of your personal information is retained in a secure location and access to these records is provided only to our employees, third party service providers and authorized representatives having a need to know and who have signed a non-disclosure agreement. Furthermore, access will be limited to the employees who require such access in the execution of their duties. However, you should be aware that absolute security does not exist on the Internet, and that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable.

### **Accuracy**

We ask that all personal information provided to us is accurate. You may update your personal information through the customer portal, if available as a feature of the service purchased.

### Questions and Enforcement

If you have any questions with respect to this Privacy Policy or otherwise related to the management or accuracy of personal information, please contact our Vice President of Internal Audit as follows:

**Vice President of Internal Audit**  
Internap Corporation  
One Ravinia Drive, Suite 1300  
Atlanta, GA 30346  

Internap will refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Safe Harbor, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by us, please visit the BBB EU Safe Harbor website at <http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints> for more information or to file a complaint. If you are a Canadian user and are unhappy with the results of any such inquiries, you may contact the provincial privacy commissioner located in the province in which you reside.

### Changes to Policy

If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post an updated Privacy Policy on our website(s) in advance of the changes taking effect. If we use personal information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will post an update to notify users. The changes to the Privacy Policy will become effective when the revised Privacy Policy is posted on our website(s). Your continued use of the website(s) and the services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy.  If any change materially affects the privacy of your personal information, we will post the Privacy Policy before its effective date and give you a reasonable period of time to object to any changes (which you may do by ceasing to use the website(s) and/or our services).
